好的  做得很好  你做得很好
Okay, you're doing good. You're doing good.
你还在拍吗
You've still got the thing.
这破摄像机还开着呢
The stupid thing is still on.
老妈  别对我嚷嚷
Mom, you don't have to yell at me.
我临盆都快12个多小时了  贾丝廷
I've been in labor for over a dozen hours, Justine.
我必须大喊出来
I have to yell.
我以为你不会来了
I thought you were gonna miss the whole thing.
妈  我开车过来要3个小时
Mom, it's a three-hour drive.
所以昨天我羊水破了的时候
That's why I called you yesterday
就打电话给你了
after my water broke.
对不起  一个合伙人扔给我了份材料
I'm sorry. A partner just dropped a brief on my desk.
很好  你做得很好
Okay, you're doing good.
是的
Yeah, right.
我了解  但是家事为先
I remember what it's like, but family comes first.
继续用力
I need you to keep pushing.
我看到宝宝的脑袋了
I can see her head.
好的  加把劲  做得很好
All right, come on. We're doing good here.
拍下来  这正是我想要的
Get this. This is what I wanted.
当然了
Gross.
你胎头着冠了
You're crowning.
你拍下  拍下来了没
Are you getting-- getting this?
差不多  有点不像阴道
Kind of. Well, not the actual vagina.
那是你的小妹妹
It's your baby sister!
这是我老妈的阴道
It's my mother's vagina.
-啊  -肩膀出来了
- Aah!  - Freeing the shoulders.
天呐  她出来了
Oh! My god! There she is.
把新生儿重症监护组叫来
Get the NICU team in here.
婴儿缺氧
Baby's hypoxic.
出什么问题了吗
Is something wrong?
-怎么了  -我不知道
- What's going on? - I don't know.
我的孩子  我的宝宝怎么样了
My baby! How's my baby?
你们在干什么啊
What are you doing?
他们在说什么
What are they saying?
我不听清楚
I can't tell.
搞清楚到底怎么回事
Find out what's going on!
请回避一下  把摄像机关掉
You need to back up. Turn that off.
婴儿丧失反应
She's not responding.
发生什么事了
What's happening?
我的孩子怎么了
What's wrong with my baby?
为什么没人理我
Why doesn't someone talk to me?
取消你们的晚餐计划
Cancel your dinner plans.
病史很短  她只有8个小时大
Short on medical history. She's only eight hours old.
虽然她不缺大夫
What she's not short on is doctors.
但可惜的是  没有一个医生
Unfortunately, none of them
可以解决她的呼吸问题
have been able to solve her breathing problems.
肺发育不全
Immature lungs?
足月妊娠  而且之前用过表面活性剂
Full term, and they gave her surfactant.
似乎发育很完善
Looks like they're fully developed.
借一步说话
I need you a minute.
默读时间  我很快回来
Silent reading time till I get back.
我的保姆来电话了
My nanny called.
她女儿今晚有独舞表演
Her daughter has a dance recital tonight.
晚上她带不了孩子
She can't work late.
我今晚要开董事会
And I have a board meeting tonight.
你有麻烦了
That's a problem.
我妈妈来不了  晚上要上烹饪课
My mother can't come. She has a cooking class.
麻烦大了
Oh, you've really got a problem.
要是有个成年人在这么十万火急的时候
If only there were some mature adult in my life
能帮我一把该多好啊
who could pinch hit in emergencies like this.
很乐意效劳  可惜的是
Love to, but I'm catching up
裸体小丑们正找我有事呢
on my back issues of Nudist Circus.
你应该看看帐篷里的胖女士
You should see what the fat lady's got
都干了些什么
under her big top.
我只是要找个人顶一下
All I need is a warm body.
她基本很快就会睡着的
She'll be asleep the entire time.
我这儿有个生病的宝宝  她需要我
I got a sick baby here who needs me.
可你们家宝宝很健壮
Yours is healthy.
你可以用电话和你的手下们沟通啊
You could deal with your team by phone.
不如等你回来的时候给我点甜头如何
How about a little something extra when you get home?
我可不会用肉体来和你讨价还价
I'm not bargaining sex for babysitting.
除此之外  你还欠我的
Besides, you owe me.
-欠你什么  -性别
- For what?  - Sex.
办公室里我还是没有看到女医生
I still don't see a female doctor in that room.
这样我会很不爽
It's making me very unhappy.
好吧  我就昧着良心干一回
Fine. Out of the goodness of my heart,
好让你高兴
which will make you happy,
好让你更需要我
which will make you desire me more,
那会转化为更猛烈的爱欲
which will turn into more sex.
7点准时到我家
Be at my place at 7:00.
捐精卡上并未标注
The sperm donor card from the father
婴儿的父亲有哮喘史
did note a history of asthma.
如果肺部症状的原因不是出在肺上呢
What if her lung problems are not coming from her lungs?
心脏看上去没什么问题
Her heart looks fine.
她的肝转移酶指标升高了
Her liver enzymes are elevated.
肝脏衰竭的时候  肝脏就停止制造蛋白了
When the liver fails, it stops producing proteins.
尤其是那些可以保证血浆限制在血管内
Specifically the ones that keep your plasma
而不是跑到肺里的那些蛋白质
inside your blood vessels and outside your lungs.
修复肝功能  她就能呼吸顺畅到
Fix the liver, she'll have enough breath
让整个病房兴奋一整夜了
to keep the entire ward up all night.
福曼  你被留堂了
Foreman, you need to stay after school.
我似乎应该道歉
I apparently need to apologize.
上周  我不该跳过你
Last week, I should not have gone over your head
就让奇斯去雇新人
and allowed Chase to hire a new team member.
你去雇个廊桥遗梦的女主角来吧
So go hire someone who liked The Bridges of Madison County.
你是想让我雇个白人女孩吗
Do you want me to hire a white girl?
找个女人来
Go find a woman,
把你自鸣得意的笑容收起来
and wipe that self-satisfied grin off your face.
很快就好
This'll be quick.
我一整周都在面试
I've been interviewing people all week.
已经筛选到了两位候选人
I have it narrowed down to two candidates.
很好  锁定一位就可以了
Well, narrow it down to one
只要赶在卡迪拿性别说事之前就可以
before Cuddy starts withholding sex.
她没有和我提过这事啊
Uh, she hasn't said anything to me about that.
我说了  别得意了
I said, wipe the grin.
是的  她很好
Yeah, she's fine.
我看着电视都能听到她的呼吸声
I can hear her breathing on the monitor.
我刚看过她
I just checked.
我每十分钟都会看一遍
I'm checking every ten minutes.
行  我再看一回
Fine. I'll check again.
她睡着的样子太可爱了
Oh, she's so cute when she's asleep.
你真应该看一看
You should see this.
她  她把一只小手放在头上
She's--she's--she's got one hand over her head.
好吧  你想待多久就多久
Okay, well, you take as long as you need.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
你老妈说不能喝  她很坏是吧
Your mommy says no, 'cause she's mean.
如果你归我管的话
If it was up to me...
我要喝果汁
Juice!
不行
No.
回床上去
Go back to bed.
我说了  回床上去
I said bed!
威尔森  想来个男孩狂欢夜吗
Wilson, hey. You up for a boys' night in?
信不信由你  呼吸问题
Believe it or not, breathing problems
可以因肝脏问题引起
can be caused by a liver problem.
那么她的肝脏怎么了
Then what's wrong with her liver?
或许是肝脓肿
Probably an abscess.
如果超声能证实
If we find it with the ultrasound,
我们就可以抽干脓肿  她就好了
we can drain it, make her better.
到周末你就能带她出院回家了
You'll be able to take her home by the end of the week.
她在出血吗
Is she bleeding?
那是静脉穿刺点渗出来的
She's oozing from her IV site.
这是肝衰竭的征状
It's a symptom of liver failure.
这证实了我们的猜测
It's what we would expect to see.
程医生  我们需要备一个单位的血
Dr. Cheng, we might need a unit of blood over here.
肝脏有回声区
Echogenic area in the liver.
你能标出来吗
Can you make it out?
看上去似乎没有
Doesn't seem to have the thick walls
脓肿该有的厚壁
you'd expect from an abscess.
抬高左肩  让我们看清楚点
Lift her left shoulder so we can get a better look.
可以让我来吗  我还没有抱过她呢
Oh, can I do it? I haven't been able to hold her yet.
她身上接的管子和静脉通道太多了
Uh, she's hooked up to too many tubes and IVs.
至少让我献点血吧
Can I at least donate blood?
当然可以
Of course.
这儿完事后  我们就会给你抽血
We'll draw your blood and see if you're a match
看看血型配不配
as soon as we're done here.
那绝对不会是脓肿
That's definitely not an abscess.
看上去像是扩张的胆管
It looks like dilated bile ducts.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我还能很快带她回家吗
Can I still take her home soon?
的确是由肝脏引起的
You were right about the liver.
超声显示
On ultrasound, we found
有肝内胆管扩张
intrahepatic dilated bile ducts.
肝外胆管是正常的
Extrahepatic ducts were normal.
有梗阻性包块吗
Are there any masses causing an obstruction?
没有  你没事吧
No. Are you okay?
我只是说话温柔了点
Just talking in a soothing voice.
和你们没关系
Not for your benefit.
怎么了  让你们感觉很爽
Why? Is it turning you on?
豪斯  我要介绍个新人你认识
House, there's someone here I need you to meet.
我刚刚雇了克里斯蒂娜·费莎大夫
I just hired Dr. Christina Fraser.
她有海外认证的
She's a board certified--
很高兴认识你  你被开除了
Nice to meet you. You're fired.
什么
What?
豪斯  你在开玩笑吧
House, you're kidding, right?
我详细调查过  她是这些人中最棒的
I've done my due diligence. She's the best there is.
我做了什么
What did I do?
很不幸
You had the misfortune
你成了我用来教训福曼的工具
to be the lesson that Foreman is learning.
福曼自负的
That whooshing sound
小肺肺一定快气炸了
is the air being let out of his ego.
你真是混蛋  豪斯
You are such an ass, House.
要整我换个法子
You could have made the same point
不要拿年轻医生的前途开玩笑
without crushing the hopes of a young doctor
她真的对这份工作满怀激情
who was actually excited to have this job.
可我不确定我有没有激情
No, I'm not sure I could have.
我想你是太相信我了
I think you give me far too much credit.
陶博  轮到你去找一个年轻医生了
Taub, it's your turn to find a young doctor
要一个真的对这份工作满怀激情的
who's actually excited to have this job.
找来让你开除吗
For you to fire?
不会  除非你们想要这样
Not until you or she earns it.
胆管扩张可能是先天性的
Dilated bile ducts could be congenital.
也就意味着胆管内部狭窄
That means that it's a stricture in the ducts themselves.
卡罗里综合症[肝内胆管囊性扩张综合症]
Caroli's syndrome.
那么  给她开刀吧
So, open her up.
手术
Surgery?
这可是个有肝衰竭的新生儿
This is a newborn with liver failure.
她的每个穿刺点都在渗血
She's oozing blood from every puncture site.
给她开刀太危险了
It's insanely risky to open her up.
是的  不幸的是手术是唯一解决途径
Yes. It's unfortunately also the only way to fix her.
用小小的手术刀给她来个小小的切口
So make teeny, tiny incisions with a really small scalpel.
我得挂了
Gotta go.
你说你已经买过单了
You told me you gave them your credit card.
而你蠢到会相信我
And you were dumb enough to believe me.
卡迪70分钟后回来
Cuddy'll be back in an hour and ten minutes.
我65分钟后回来
I'll be back in an hour and five.
不  你不能
Oh, no, you don't.
我就这样
Oh, yes, I do.
你不是要丢下宝宝吧
You're not gonna leave the kid?
是的  因为和你不同
Yes, I am, 'cause unlike you,
我没什么良心
I don't have a conscience.
但和你不同的是
And unlike you,
我可没和卡迪嘿咻
I'm not having sex with Cuddy,
所以我才能走
so I actually can leave.
你在唬我
You're bluffing.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你不能丢下一个不满两岁的孩子不管
You're not gonna leave a two-year-old unattended.
我能啊  我把她留给你了
True. I'm leaving her with you.
一个有责任感的成年人
A responsible adult.
你最好回屋里去
Better get back in there.
孩子一个人呢
Kid's all alone.
你不觉得心烦吗
It's kind of bugging you, isn't it?
和我没关系
Not my problem.
客观来讲
Well, since, objectively,
你比我更在乎一个孤独的小孩
you care more about leaving a child alone than I do,
你会想照顾她
it kind of is.
客观地说  我没有揽过这活
Objectively, since I never accepted this responsibility,
我不会管的
it kind of isn't.
没错  但你还是会留下  本性难改
True, and yet it is. Because you're you.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
是我要走了
你不会走的  你做不到
You're not gonna leave. You can't.
算你狠
Fine.
你说对了
You're right.
知道我会怎么做吗
You know what I can do?
我会进屋  然后打电话叫个顾婴服务
I can go in there and call a babysitting service
每小时15块  再给卡迪打电话
for 15 bucks an hour, then call Cuddy
告诉她谁在看孩子  还有原因
and tell her who's watching her kid and why.
你留下  我就不走
I'll stay if you stay.
咱们只离开了两分钟啊
We were gone two minutes.
你嘴里是什么  甜心
What have you got there, sweetie?
来  吐出来
Come on now, spit it out.
来  甜心  张嘴
Come on, sweetie. Open.
张嘴
Open.
瑞秋  你吃了几枚硬币
Rachel, how many coins did you eat?
隔离胆总管
Isolating the common bile duct.
插入套管末端
And mobilizing the distal end for cannulation.
血压降到50了
Bp is down to 50 systolic.
你得停止插套管了
You've got to stop the cannulation.
我还没开始
I haven't started yet.
给她注射一剂肾上腺素
Hit her with a bolus of phenylephrine.
这样可以有足够时间插入胆管
That should buy us enough time to get in the bile ducts.
血压升起来了  70
BP is rising. 70 systolic.
很好  进入总胆管了
Nice. I'm in the common bile duct.
接下来插入胆囊管
Advancing past the cystic duct.
目前为止还没有狭窄或堵塞
No strictures or blockages so far.
血压又下降了
BP is dropping again.
要再注射一剂肾上腺素吗
Another bolus of phenylephrine.
不能再注射了
She can't take more.
第一剂还在起作用
The first bolu is still doing the effect.
血压仍在下降
BP is still dropping.
我们得取出管子了  手术中止
We've got to pull out. We're done.
我都差不多插进去了
I was barely in.
这说不通啊
This doesn't make sense.
光是肝脏问题
The liver problem alone
是不会影响婴儿的血压的
is not gonna mess with the baby's BP.
不管是什么问题  肯定影响心脏了
Whatever this is, it's got to be affecting her heart.
心脏和肝脏
Heart plus the liver.
可能是结节状硬化
Could be tuberous sclerosis.
或者是肝脏内的
Or it could be a vascular malformation
血管畸形  引起了这两个症状
in the liver, causing both problems.
你们觉得程医生怎么样
So what do you guys think of Dr. Cheng?
治疗血管畸形最好的方法就是手术
Best treatment for a vascular malformation is surgery.
我觉得你老婆肯定不希望
And I think your wife thinks
你对程医生有想法
you shouldn't think anything of Dr. Cheng.
不能做手术了
No surgery.
一个新生儿不能再承受一次手术了
A newborn baby can't handle another trip to the O.R.
我不是说有想法
I didn't mean think think.
我是说聘用她的可能性
I meant think as a potential hire.
我们给孩子用类固醇
What if we started the baby on steroids
加上血管再生药物和多巴胺怎么样
an anti-angiogenesis agent, and dopamine?
会和手术的效果一样的
Could work just as well as surgery.
关闭那些坏血管
Snap those bad blood vessels shut.
我打电话给豪斯确认一下
I'll call House to get approval.
那  你耸肩是什么意思
So, what was that shrug?
是表示"程医生大概能行"
A "Dr. Cheng could work" shrug?
还是表示
Or a "House is gonna crush you
"豪斯会阻止你考虑她"
for even considering her" shrug?
你真混蛋
You suck.
豪斯会讨厌我们请的任何人
House is gonna hate anyone we hire,
因为他不想雇人
because he doesn't want to hire anyone.
那么你觉得我应该放弃?
So you think I should abstain?
把问题扔回给他?
Just give the decision back to him?
那他又会损你是个窝囊废
Then he'll just mock you for being a wuss.
你纠结吧
You're screwed.
除非豪斯觉得雇用她是他自己的主意
Unless House feels like hiring her is his idea.
还是不接
Still not answering.
我们开始治疗吧
We should just start the treatment.
她开了袋中国食品
She opened up a Chinese food bag
然后吃了硬币
to eat money.
真白痴
What an idiot.
是的  你点了木须肉
Okay, you ordered the moo shoo pork
和宫保鸡丁外卖  没错吧
and the orange cashew chicken, right?
我通常都点这两道菜
Like I always order.
你收拾完外面了吗
Did you clean up in there?
对  完美如初
Yeah. It's good enough.
所以  扣掉税
Okay, so with tax,
找零应该是68分
the change should have been 68 cents.
外面只有58分
There's only 58 cents out there.
丢了一角
There's a dime missing.
也可能是他少找你钱了
Well, he could have shortchanged you.
冰箱贴啥也没吸到
Fridge magnet's not getting anything.
因为那不过是个冰箱贴
That's because it's a fridge magnet,
而且除非她吞了加拿大币
and unless she swallowed a Canadian dime,
一般硬币是没磁力的
it's not magnetic.
真的吗
Really?
我说  小孩总是爱吞东西的  对吧
I mean, kids swallow things all the time, right?
她吞了一毛钱  会拉出来的
I mean, she swallowed a dime, she poops it out.
-她会没事的  -没错
- She'll be fine.  - Absolutely.
除非硬币黏在肠壁上
Unless it gets stuck in her intestine
引起堵塞  她会因此死掉
and causes a blockage, which could kill her.
那可不太好
Then she won't be fine.
你必须告诉卡迪
You have to tell Cuddy.
那我就不好过了
Well, then I won't be fine.
如果你不告诉卡迪
If you don't tell Cuddy,
我会出去亲自告诉她
I will go out there and tell her myself.
是吗  你要告诉她什么
Yeah? What are you gonna tell her?
难道说你把硬币放在外面
Are you gonna tell her that you left coins out
把孩子自己留在家吗
and you left her child unsupervised?
你别把这事赖在我头上
Hey, hey, hey! You are not gonna pin this on me!
瑞秋需要24小时观察
Rachel needs to be monitored for 24 hours
看那一毛钱会不会出来
to see that the dime passes.
你知道的  确保别让她死了
You know, just to make sure she doesn't die.
你怎么在教我做事的时候
You're telling me to do the right thing
自己在往窗户外爬
while climbing out a window?
告诉她
Tell her!
她醒过吗
Did she wake up at all?
醒过一次
One time.
她通常不这样啊  她没事吧
That's not like her. Is she all right?
她很好
She's fine.
我留下过夜怎么样
How about I stay the night?
你就能好好谢我了
Then you can really thank me.
我明天得早起
I have to get up early.
不能睡过头
Won't be able to sleep in.
我一向睡很沉
I'm a deep sleeper.
轮班了
Round two.
贾丝廷回家了吗
Did Justine go home?
她说下楼几分钟
Said she was going downstairs for a few minutes.
已经过了几小时了
A few hours ago.
你们俩很亲密吗
So you two are close?
事实上比以前好多了
Well, it's been getting better actually.
至少她还在这栋楼里
At least she's here in the building.
对她来说很难了
That's pretty supportive for her.
怎么了
What is it?
她变粉红色了
She's pinker.
不好吗
Is that bad?
很好
That's good.
非常好
That's very good.
她怎么了
Was that her?
我能抱抱她吗
Can I hold her?
我想你们都期盼许久了
I think it's long overdue.
终于头一回抱上了
My first time. Finally.
技术上讲  是第二次吧
Technically, it's your second time.
我不是那意思
I didn't mean--
我知道  妈妈
I know, mom.
看着像是血管畸形
Looks like it was a vascular malformation.
格罗根宝宝现在好些了
The Grogan baby is better.
不错嘛
Nice job.
准备了哦  亲爱的
Okay, ready, honey.
一动也不要动  屏住呼吸
So stay very, very still and hold your breath.
千万别动哦
Don't move.
她动了  没一个听话的
She moved. They always move.
有份很好的工作  作诊断
It is a good job. Diagnostics.
解答迷题  拯救生命
Solve a mystery, save a life.
但我想你可能更喜欢儿科
But I suppose you're pretty attached to pediatrics?
不好意思  杨女士
I'm sorry, Ms. Young,
我想请您按住您女儿别动
but I'm gonna have to ask you to restrain your daughter.
现在这位妈妈肯定不乐意了
Now the mom's not gonna want to do it
她情愿
because she'd rather I just keep
我一直用话筒说她女儿
blasting her daughter with radiation.
你是在说
You're telling me
豪斯部门有个空缺职位吗
there's an opening in House's department?
你有兴趣吗
Would you be interested?
再没有小孩  再没有家长
No more kids, no more parents.
一次只有一个病例而非十七个
One case at a time instead of 17?
安排我面试吧
Set up the interview.
可能你并不需要面试
It's possible you won't need to interview.
放松  我来
Relax, I got this.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
没事  抱歉  我还是个新手
Yeah, sorry, I'm just new to all this.
要我帮你重设闹钟吗
You want me to reset the alarm?
老天  别
God, no.
案子尽在掌控
Case is under control.
我要睡个懒觉
I'm sleeping in.
你的老板真是大爱你啊
Your boss must really like you.
早啊  玛丽娜
Hey, Marina.
意粉在冰箱里  可以当午饭
Pasta's in the fridge for lunch.
你一大清早打给我电话
I assume, since you're calling so early,
我想是手术非常成功吧
that the surgery was a rousing success.
你竟然还以为
And I assume, since you still think
我们真做手术了
we actually did the surgery,
我想你是有八小时没看过手机了吧
you haven't checked your messages in eight hours.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我想这就是你们这些人
I believe this is what your people term
所谓的垃圾电话
a poopie call.
那叫招妓电话
Uh, the word is Booty.
我是不知道你们在干什么
Well, I don't know what you're doing,
但这就是个垃圾电话
but this is a poopie call.
不是卡罗里综合症
It's not Caroli's syndrome.
程医生找到
Dr. Cheng spotted a--
等等等等  你说什么
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what?
我知道有犹太人  黑人和鳄鱼猎人
I know about the jew, the black, and the croc hunter,
可我们什么时候带亚洲人玩了
but when did we get our Asian persuasion on?
程医生在新生儿重症监护病房参与这案子
Dr. Cheng is the NICU attending on the case.
她现在不在这里
And she's not here.
那我就是白费口舌了
Well, then I just wasted a perfectly good racial epithet.
她在宝宝的肝脏
She spotted a vascular malformation
发现了血管畸形
in the baby's liver.
恭喜你
Good call.
没有你说的废话这就不是垃圾电话了
Except for everything you just said.
我们的病人不可能有血管畸形
There's no way that our patient has a vascular malformation.
你能根据不在场所收集的大量信息
And you can tell that from the vast amount of information
肯定的得到这一答案吗
you've gleaned from not being here?
要记住她急性腰部外伤性劳损程度
Don't need to be there to remember
是常人的三倍  不用我到场
that the patient's A.L.T.S were three times normal.
宝宝的肝损伤范围大得很
The baby's liver damage is far too extensive.
程医生就是个白痴
Dr. Cheng's an idiot.
公平起见  这不完全是她的主意
In fairness, it wasn't completely her idea.
主要是福曼的
More of a Foreman kind of thing.
那你就是个超级大白痴
Well, then you're an even bigger idiot
还想为她扯谎
for trying to cover for her.
豪斯  我们按血管畸形进行治疗
House, we treated for a vascular malformation,
她确实好转了
and she got better.
不  她没有
No, she didn't.
她再次病发时给我电话
Call me when she crashes again.
结果还不错
That went well.
有什么事吗
Everything okay?
说吧  我认得这表情
Come on. I know that look.
我只是不习惯看到你这样真情流露
I'm just not used to seeing such emotion coming from you.
我刚生了孩子
I just gave birth.
整个母爱泛滥啊
I'm, like, one big vat of hormones right now.
不只是荷尔蒙的关系  妈妈
It's not just the hormones, mom.
你对她很特别
You're different with her.
这样没事  很好  只是
It's okay. It's good. It's just...
我不禁要想  在我成长时
I can't help thinking, where was this mom
这样的妈妈在哪里
when I was growing up?
我从没想过
Wow. I never realized you considered me
你认为我是个失败的母亲
such a failure as a mother.
我不觉得你失败
I don't consider you a failure.
我只是
I just--
我从来不知道你还有充满母爱的一面
I never knew that there was an alternative.
我觉得她尿湿了
Hmm. I think she feels wet.
你能抱一下她吗
Can you hold her a sec?
我去拿片尿布
I'm gonna grab a diaper.
好的
Okay.
妈妈  不太对劲
Mom, something's wrong.
护士  她又出血了
Oh! Nurse! She's bleeding again!
好的  她在办公室
All right, she's in her office.
动作快点
Move fast.
如果你看到她挪着丰满的屁股过来
You see a double-wide tuchus coming this way,
就跟姑娘似的叫吧
you scream like a girl.
如果瑞秋醒了
If Rachel wakes up,
她会一五一十的告诉卡迪的
she's gonna tell Cuddy everything.
她才两岁
She's two.
昨晚她一直在哭诉
Last night, she was whining
她窗口外的大麋鹿
about the giant moose that lives outside her window.
美杜莎[指卡迪]在六点种方向
Medusa at 6:00.
别回头  快走快走
Don't look back. Move, move.
你好
Hello.
你好啊  我是住在你房间外面的
Hello, I'm the friendly moose who lives
友好麋鹿
outside your bedroom.
她讨厌那只麋鹿
She hates that moose.
给我超声耦合剂
Hand me the gel.
好的
Okay.
长话短说
Make it short.
别话里有话的
Do not pardon the pun.
她又病发了  你在哪里
She's crashing again. Where are you?
我得先明白你在说什么
Is it actually important that I understand what you say?
什么
What?
说吧
Yeah?
宝宝又出血了
The baby's bleeding again.
我好惊讶啊
I'm shocked.
不对  等等  惊讶的是你才对
Oh, no, wait a minute. That's you.
没错  你就是个天才
Yes. You're a genius.
出血说明她的肝脏仍在衰竭
The bleeding means her liver is still failing.
不是血管畸形
It's not a vascular malformation.
豪斯  过来看这个
House, come take a look at this.
继续思考
Hold that thought.
豪斯  别  我需要你
House, no! I need you!
刚通过回盲瓣
Just past the ileocecal valve.
什么都没有
It's nothing.
只是个不规则的东西
It's just an irregularity.
那是个一角硬币
It's a dime.
也可能是一团空气
Or a pocket of air.
是啊  还有富兰克林·罗斯福的头像在上面
Yeah, with FDR's face on it.
那不是人头  是阴影
That's not a face. It's a shadow.
豪斯  这东西就是个标准圆
House, the thing is perfectly round.
移到边上看看
Well, move the wand to the side.
-痒痒  -因为我是挠痒痒怪兽
- Tickles!  - That's because I'm the tickle monster.
我要继续挠你痒痒
Gonna tickle you even more!
看那个
Look at--look at that.
需要做个X光检查来确认
We need an X-ray to be sure.
好主意  尽管给她做无谓的放射吧
Great, just give her an unnecessary dose of radiation.
这就是一角硬币
It's a dime.
豪斯  我知道你在里面
House, I know you're in there.
快开门
Open the door!
我看到你的分机号了
I saw your extension on the call.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing down here?
威尔森遇到个两岁的癌症病患
Uh, Wilson's got a two-year-old with cancer.
她很痛苦  真叫人难过
She's in a lot of pain. It's very sad.
他的临床礼节很到位
He also has an outstanding bedside manner.
她肝衰竭的情况更糟了
Her liver failure is getting worse.
你是对的  现在怎么办
You were right. Now what?
有趣的是她为什么先好转
The interesting question is not why she's worse now
而非现在才恶化
but why she got better in the first place.
可能是我们的治疗
Could have been something we did that temporarily
暂时缓解了
relieved the--
你们给她用了什么
What'd you put her on again?
输血以后  我们给她用了类固醇
After the transfusion, we gave her steroids,
多巴胺  和抗...
dopamine, and the anti--
类固醇能治疗先天性肝硬化
steroids can treat idiopathic hepatic fibrosis.
这能解释她为什么先好转后恶化
It would explain why she got better and then worse.
但不能解释多个胆管扩张
But not the multiple dilated ducts.
豪斯  你进来一下
House, I need you back in here!
癌症比肝病严重
Cancer kid trumps liver kid.
抱歉  天机不可泄露  规矩你懂的
Sorry. Confidentiality. There are rules, you know.
这就是个一角硬币
That is a dime.
它在移动
It looks mobile.
还在结肠中间
And it's right in the middle of the colon.
拉粑粑的最佳地段
Prime location for pooping out.
给她吃点轻泻剂帮助它出来
We'll give her some laxatives to help it on its way.
看来  有人能吃到
Sounds to me like someone's going to get
好吃的巧克力啦
some yummy chocolate.
巧克力  香香啊
Chocolate. Yum yum yum.
你将来一定是个好妈妈
You're gonna make a great mommy one day.
多谢相候
Thanks for waiting.
把婴儿连接到母体
Hook the mom up to the baby.
直接输血
Direct blood transfusion.
然后呢
And what else?
没然后
Nothing else.
太神奇了  她的肤色变粉症状也好转了
It's amazing. She's pink and healthy again.
都是因为母亲的爱抚
Mother's touch.
简直是奇迹  谢谢你们
It's a miracle. Thank you.
输血并不是治疗方案
A blood transfusion isn't a cure.
也非奇迹
Or a miracle.
那为什么婴儿看起来像是痊愈了
Then why does the baby seem like she's cured?
不知道
I have no idea.
我们要么让病人
Our patient can either go through life
连着世界上最长的"脐带"过一生
with the world's longest umbilical cord,
要么开始神奇血液的鉴别诊断
or we can discuss the differential for magic blood.
婴儿的血氧含量稳定
Baby's O2 sats are holding.
你要么是程医生
Either you're Dr. Cheng
要么是太早来给我美甲了
or you're early for my mani-pedi.
我原以为她的专长能...
I thought her expertise could--
能告诉我们血氧含量
Could tell us the O2 sats.
我希望你能有些独到的见解
I hope you come with some original ideas.
两种可能  要么是母亲特殊血液
Either the mom's blood is special,
能够治疗某种病症
which would mean it's treating something specific,
这就意味着婴儿患有某种疾病
which means the baby has a disease.
不然母亲的血就只是普通的血
Or mom's blood is just blood,
但是补充了婴儿体内缺乏的物质
and it's replacing something the baby is missing,
这就意味着婴儿只是先天不足
which means the baby has a simple deficiency.
鉴于她的肝功能衰竭  很可能是
Given the liver failure, a deficiency of clotting factors,
缺少凝血因子  酶或者维生素
enzymes, or vitamins are the most likely.
那就找出来吧
So let's find out.
给婴儿输其他人的血
Hook the baby up to someone else's blood
看她是否好转
and see if she gets better.
-找个捐献者  -我是0型阴性血
- Find a donor. - I'm O negative.
万能输血者
Universal donor.
那就由你来输血
Hook yourself up.
程医生  挂上我
Dr. Cheng, hook me up.
跟我走
Walk with me.
我的小组对你很有好感
My team seems to have taken a shine to you.
我也喜欢他们
I like them too.
我猜你跟我们混是因为想要这份工作
I assume you're hanging around because you want a job.
猜得没错
That would be a fair assumption.
那我得考你一下
Well, I'm gonna have to test you.
比如说  两岁大的孩子...
Let's say, two-year-old...
20小时之前吞下一枚硬币
swallowed a coin 20 hours ago.
她不会有事的  对吗
She's gonna be fine, right?
有梗阻的现象吗
Any signs of obstruction?
为了达到测试你的目的
For the purposes of this quiz,
我当然要说  还没有
let's say, not yet.
我会开些泻药
I'd give a laxative,
但我不会等太久
although I wouldn't wait too long.
她的肠子有可能会局部缺血
Her bowel could become ischemic,
更糟的话  可能发生肠套叠
or worse, an intussusception.
太久是多久
Define "Too long."
最多再等六个小时
Another six hours, max.
到那时候  她的身体已经排空了
By then, her system is clear.
如果没出来  就不会出来了
If it's not out, it's not coming out.
然后我该做什么
And then what do I do?
我是说  你该做什么  这是你的考题
I mean, what do you do? It's your test.
我会做内镜  把它取出来
I'd go in with a scope and get it.
我合格了吗
Did I pass?
我说了不算  找陶博去吧
It's not up to me. Talk to Taub.
躲在男厕所里
Men's room?
事实证明  现在这种情况下厕所更方便
It turns out, toilets are handy in this situation,
而且我相对确信卡迪不会进来
and I felt relatively sure that Cuddy wouldn't come in.
卡迪进来过
Oh, Cuddy's been in here.
真的吗
Seriously?
做...  这地方也太糟糕了
This must be a terrible place to have se--uhh!
天下哪有糟糕的地儿
Is there such a place?
再等六小时
Okay, six more hours,
还不行我们就做内镜  把它取出来
then we're going in with a scope and pulling it out.
给一个两岁孩子做内镜  太危险了
Scope a two-year-old? It's dangerous.
是你一直在提醒我
And as you keep pointing out,
这枚角币划破她的内脏同样危险
so is a dime ripping through her intestines.
六个小时之后卡迪就回家了
Cuddy will be home from work in six hours.
但是没关系  我就大叫  "看那边"
But no big deal. I'll just scream, "Look over there,"
你趁此机会迅速把内镜伸进她女儿的直肠
while you quickly shove a scope up her daughter's rectum.
我可以主动帮忙看孩子
I could offer to baby-sit again,
-让她出去玩一晚  -当然
- let her have the night out. - Sure.
你主动帮忙  她绝对不会起疑的
That won't raise any suspicions.
我开始后悔从不做好人了
I wish I was nicer.
把你的辐射剂量计徽章给我
Hey. Give me your radiation dosimeter.
为什么
Why?
因为它跟我眼睛颜色很搭
Because it matches my eyes.
我觉得这样不管用
I think we can say this isn't working.
我们可以继续给她输你的血
We'll get her back on your blood.
暂时可以维持
That'll help for now.
但这说明是感染造成的
But this means there's an infection.
首先  我们要确定病因
First we need to identify it.
我们知道是肝部的问题  所以要先取样
We know it's in her liver, so we'll get a sample.
然后我们才能知道怎样治好她
Then we can figure out how to help her get better.
我要这个孩子
I had this baby
是因为我想做一次特别的妈妈
because I wanted a chance to be a special mom.
但不是这种
But not this way.
放射科出了点问题
Problems in radiology.
一枚辐射剂量计徽章显示辐射过量
A radiation dosimeter badge turned positive.
可能是哪台断层扫描仪发生耗散
I could have a CT Scanner that's leaking
或者哪里洒了一瓶铊
or a spilled vial of thallium somewhere.
我还不知道是谁的徽章
I don't even know whose badge it was.
代码被划掉了
The code was scratched off.
一定是有人故意的
That had to be intentional.
-谁会  -不知道
- Why would anyone... - I don't know.
我只知道我要加班了
All I know is that I'm gonna need to work late.
实际上  我希望你能照顾下宝宝
I was actually hoping that you could baby-sit.
-不是吧  -拜托了
- No. - Please.
连着两晚当保姆
Two nights in a row?
拜托了
Please.
我也有自己的生活
I have a life, you know.
我会让你劳有所得的
I will make it worth your while.
我不会以带孩子换性福的
I am not going to bargain babysitting for sex.
谁说的这种傻话
Who the hell said that?
我当然愿意
Of course I will.
谢谢
Thank you.
那东西几乎和她一般大
Oh, that thing's nearly as big as she is.
别担心  我以前也这样做过  至少一次
Don't worry. I've done this at least once before.
再往前一厘米就到了
Advance another centimeter and you're in.
我的上帝  真可怕  是感染造成的吗
Oh, God, that looks awful. Is that from the infection?
不是  这说明我们错了
No. It means we were wrong.
那是个黑素瘤
It's a melanoma.
你是说  皮肤癌吗
You mean, like skin cancer?
她怎么可能得皮肤癌  她都没出去过
How would she get that? She's never been outside.
可是你出去过
But you have.
你是说我把癌症传给了孩子
You're saying I gave my baby cancer?
我在她左手食指指甲下面找到一颗痣
I found a mole under the nail on her left index finger.
活组织切片检查证明是黑素瘤
The biopsy revealed it's melanoma.
就这么简单
That's it?
为什么没人帮我准备食物
How come no one got me food?
"就这么简单"是什么意思  她长了黑素瘤
What do you mean, "That's it"? The woman has melanoma.
她可能会死的  如果我们不...
She could die if we don't--
无聊
Boring.
既然婴儿患有黑素瘤
Since the baby has the melanoma,
就说明母亲也有
we kind of already knew the mom had it.
没错  但现在我们知道了瘤的位置
Yes, but now we know where it is,
就可以采取有效治疗
so we can treat it much more effectively.
太好了  那就去治疗吧
Great. So treat her.
还是很无聊
Also boring.
有趣的是
What's interesting is that
妈妈的黑素瘤在子宫内传给胎儿
mom's melanoma spread to the baby in utero,
说明发生了癌细胞转移
which means it's metastatic,
也就说明已经是晚期了
which means it's late stage.
有几个黑素瘤晚期病人
How many people with a late stage melanoma
能像她这样健康
are as healthy as she is?
显然  妈妈血液中有某种物质
Clearly, something's going on in mom's blood
治疗了她和婴儿的黑素瘤
that's treating her melanoma as well as her baby's.
抗体
Antibodies.
如果她的免疫系统在攻击黑素瘤
If her immune system was fighting the melanoma,
就不会发生转移了
it never would have spread.
没错  这说明免疫系统是在攻击其它东西
Exactly, which means it's fighting something else,
而黑素瘤细被抑制是城门失火殃及池鱼
and the melanoma cells are getting caught in the crossfire.
那么母亲的免疫系统到底在攻击什么呢
So what's mom's immune system really shooting at?
硬皮病能够导致抗癌抗体的产生
Scleroderma can cause cancer-fighting antibodies.
变应性肉芽肿病综合征也可以
So can Churg Strauss,
大部分自身免疫疾病都可以
pretty much any auto-immune disease.
或者是感染造成了肉芽肿  肺结核和分歧杆菌
Or infections that cause granulomas, TB, mycobacteria.
你看  程医生
See, Dr. Cheng?
这才不叫无聊
This is not boring.
从自身免疫疾病着手
Start with auto-immune.
你去验血
Go test her blood.
把食物留下
And leave your food.
会有点儿疼
Just a little pinch.
这么说  我没有真的让她好起来
So, uh, I'm not actually making her better.
而是让她生病了
I'm making her sick.
不是你的错
You can't blame yourself.
我吃正确的食物
I ate all the right foods,
读了好多书和研究资料
I read all the books and the studies,
甚至雇私家侦探
and I even hired a private Detective
调查每一位精子捐献者
to research each sperm donor.
可我忽略了最要紧的一件事
I just missed one big thing.
我自己的癌症
My own cancer.
好了
I'm all done here.
很快就会有结果
We'll have the results soon.
如果是那种病会怎样
And if that's what this is?
自身免疫疾病
An auto-immune disease?
治疗方案很简单
Treatment's fairly simple.
如果是别的疾病呢
And if it's something else?
别急  我们一步一步来
Let's just take this one step at a time.
别折磨自己了
Stop beating yourself up.
妈妈  对不起
I'm sorry, mom.
你生病我很难过  还有我之前不该说那些话
Not just for this, but for what I said earlier.
我又气又嫉妒  才说了那些伤人的话
I was jealous and angry, and I lashed out.
你是个好妈妈
But you were a great mom.
真的是个好妈妈
You are a great mom.
我不配有你这样好的女儿
I don't deserve such a good daughter.
硬皮病阴性
Negative for scleroderma.
豪斯刚才叫你做什么
So, what did House want earlier?
他让我做了个小测试
He just gave me a little quiz
他说他同意雇用我
and said he was okay with hiring me,
不过还是要你来拿主意
but that it was your decision.
皮肌炎阴性
Negative for dermatomyositis.
他这么说只是为了给我下套
He's just saying that to set me up.
你不打算雇用我吗
So you're not offering me the job?
如果他愿意让我雇用你  其中必有原委
If he wants me to offer you the job, something's going on.
我也这样想  不是狼疮
That was my thinking too. It's not lupus.
豪斯这人办事从不直来直去
Things with House are never as simple as they seem.
相信我  他一定有隐藏的动机
Trust me, he's got an ulterior motive,
在行动之前  我一定要弄清楚
and I've got to figure it out before I do anything.
好吧
Okay.
母亲的变应性肉芽肿阴性  不是自身免疫疾病
Mom's negative for Churg Strauss. This isn't auto-immune.
该给她扫描查可能引发肉芽肿的感染了
Time to scan her for infections that could cause granulomas.
半小时内拉了3次
Third poop in the last half hour.
一无所获
Still nothing.
好  就这样了
All right, that's it.
时间到
Time's up.
执行"女武神"手术计划
Operation Valkyrie is now in effect.
管它是不是陷阱  雇她就是了
Either it's a trap or it's not. Just hire her.
肺部没有肉芽肿
Lungs clear for granulomas.
就是  谁在乎呢
Yeah, who cares?
昨天夹住你腿的捕熊器还爽吧
Did you enjoy that bear trap snapping on your leg yesterday?
你能意识到这只是个比喻义的陷阱吧
You realize it's just a metaphorical trap?
再说你的腿脚还安然无恙呢
You'll still have all your limbs.
第四根肋骨  锁骨中线附近
Fourth rib about the midclavicular line.
你想太多了
You're over-thinking this.
我选的人面还没见就被豪斯炒了
House fired my pick sight unseen.
奇斯选的谁豪斯根本不关心
He was never even interested in Chase's pick.
他只是揪住奇斯选人的原因不放
He was only obsessed with how she reflected on Chase.
陈医生是他唯一给过回应的候选人
Dr. Cheng is the only candidate he's actually responded to.
你不是想让豪斯经手吗
You wanted House invested.
他已经经手了  雇她吧
He is. Hire her.
你推理半天  还说我想太多
And you think I'm over-thinking this?
别念叨了  就雇她吧
Shut up and hire her.
看
Look.
燕麦形细胞肺癌
Oat cell lung cancer.
她患了两种癌症
She has two cancers?
癌能治癌
Cancer treating cancer?
你患了肺癌
You have lung cancer.
我不是得了皮肤癌吗
I thought I had skin cancer.
听上去匪夷所思  但你同时患有两种癌症
As unlikely as it sounds, you have both.
事实上  肺癌正在治疗皮肤癌
Actually, the lung cancer is basically treating the skin cancer.
所以你没有感觉到病痛  你的血能让孩子好转
It's why you're not feeling sick and why your blood's helping your baby.
发现及时  应该在可治范围
We found it early, so it should be treatable.
某种程度上说  是你女儿救了你
In a way, your daughter saved your life.
我们会给你安排手术  然后开始化疗
We'll get you set up for the surgery and start you on chemo.
那Kayla呢
What about Kayla?
她只需做化疗
She'll only need the chemo.
继续给她输我的血不行吗
Can't you just keep giving her my blood?
肿瘤切除之后
Not once we cut out the tumor
你的身体会停止产生抗体
your body will stop making the antibodies
你的血就不会让她好转了
that are keeping your baby healthy.
我的手术可以推迟吗
Can you hold off on my surgery?
过去一天之内你孩子的肿瘤缩小了百分之十五
Over the last day, your baby's liver tumors have shrunk 15%.
据此推算  完全消灭掉她的癌细胞
Projecting forward, it would take eight or nine days
需要八九天时间
to completely eradicate her cancer cells.
那就再等八九天
So let's take the eight or nine days...
等上八九天癌症确实不太可能扩散
The cancer probably won't spread in the next nine days,
但有其他风险
but there are other risks.
癌变使你的血液变粘稠  易形成血栓
Cancer thickens your blood, which could cause clots.
给我的孩子化疗会有什么风险
What are the risks to putting my baby on chemo?
化疗可能会造成脑损伤或影响发育
It could damage her brain or affect her development,
但相对于延缓癌症治疗对你的影响而言
but these risks are small compared to the risks
化疗的风险微乎其微
that you would be taking by leaving your cancers untreated.
-我想等  -妈
- I want to wait. - Mom.
你没听见吗  这太危险了
Are you listening? This is way too dangerous.
我愿意冒险
I'll take the risks.
我选对我女儿最有利的方案
I want what's best for my daughter.
我也是你的女儿呀
I'm your daughter too.
-她是个婴儿  你已经成年了  -那又怎样
- She's a baby. You're an adult. - So what?
我成年了就再也不需要母亲了吗
I don't need my mom anymore?
不  你向来不需要我
No. You never did.
因为我从来都不够关心你
'Cause I wasn't there for you.
可是你看  你现在多好
But look at you. You turned out great.
你才不知道我好不好
Oh, you don't know if I'm great.
你根本都不了解我
You don't know me at all.
我不会让你为了两天大的婴儿牺牲自己
And I'm not gonna let you martyr yourself for a two-day-old infant
只因为你觉得当初没能照顾好我心存内疚
just because you feel guilty because you weren't around for me.
我不是在牺牲自己  不过9天而已
I'm not martyring myself. It's nine days.
推迟手术吧
Let's hold off on the surgery.
你居然带了吃的来
You brought food?
这是医疗程序  不是晚餐约会
This is a medical procedure, not a dinner date.
我知道这是医疗程序
I'm aware that this is a delicate procedure.
我还知道我的手在抖
I'm also aware that my hands are shaking
因为我一整天没吃饭血糖很低
from low blood sugar 'cause I haven't eaten all day.
所以我此举虽然貌似不够体贴礼貌
So while this may seem insensitive,
这份木须肉却是至关重要的回春
this crucial, lifesaving moo shoo--
我的煎饼呢
where are my extra pancakes?
该死  我点的木须肉外加煎饼没给
Damn it, they forgot the extra pancakes
只要那个挑染蓝头发的新服务员一接电话
Every time that new girl with the blue streak
肯定有东西错
in her hair answers the phone, they screw up.
你那天取外卖的时候也是她当班吗
Was she there when you picked up the food?
那天你也点了外加煎饼
You ordered extra pancakes?
外加煎饼多少钱
How much did they cost?
5角5一张
55 cents.
我点了两张
And there were two.
那么所有东西加起来应该是
So that means the total on the last bill was--
应该是
was--
-18元4角2  -18元4角2
- $18.42. - $18.42.
Rachel不可能吃了角币
Rachel couldn't have eaten a dime
因为没有多余的角币了
because there was no extra dime.
太好了
Yeah.
那么我们在超声波图像上看到的
So the image that we saw on the ultrasound--
明显就是一团气泡  我早说了
was obviously just a pocket of air, like I said all along.
可你还是往最坏处想
But you saw the worst case scenario,
像所有患得患失毫无理性的父母一样
like every irrational, worried parent.
你当不了好妈妈
You'd make a terrible mommy.
不给我份饺子吗
Want to give me some dumplings?
妈妈  我给你带了些
Mom, I brought you some--
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
妈妈
Mom.
来人  快来救命
We need help in here! Somebody help us!
大规模肺栓塞
Massive pulmonary embolism.
她几秒内就死了
She died in seconds.
如果她让我们切除肿瘤就不会这样
Wouldn't have happened if she let us remove the tumor.
应该不会
Probably not.
尸检之后  我们采了她的血
Postmortem, we were able to harvest all of her blood.
足够治疗婴儿了
It's enough to treat the baby.
也算死得其所
That's something.
很神奇的一个病例
Pretty amazing case.
多谢你的帮助
Thanks for your help.
有机会与你们共事我很开心
I was glad for the chance to work it with you.
我考虑过了
I've thought about it,
我现在正式请你接受这份工作
and I'd like to formally offer you the job.
真好笑  我本来很想在豪斯的团队做事
It's funny, I wanted to work on House's team,
现在合作做之后却不想了
until I started working with his team.
我知道  奇斯和福曼有时候有点儿
Yeah, I know. Chase and Foreman can get a little...
其实  是因为你
Actually, it's you.
豪斯做事混蛋我明白  至少他有资本
I get that House is an ass, but at least he owns it.
你不明白
You don't understand.
这件事不过是豪斯的一个游戏
This whole thing was just a game to House.
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
你是个大人  陶博医生
You're a grown man, Dr. Taub.
你怎样选择完全由你做主
You can make whatever choices you want,
豪斯说你可以雇用我的时候  你不但没有
and instead of hiring me when he said you could,
反而怕得要死  疑神疑鬼像个小孩子
you chose to act like a paranoid, scared little kid.
我讨厌小孩
I hate kids.
陶博医生  再会
Good-bye, Dr. Taub.
我一定会让你永远不会忘记她
I'll make sure you never forget her
和她为你做的一切
and what she did for you.
她一直努力成为世上最好的妈妈
She was just trying to be the best mom in the world.
她就是最好的妈妈
She was.
这回该你了
This one's all yours.
不帮忙了吗
What happened to helping out?
帮过了
I did.
是谁便便了哦
Did someone go poopie?
怎么回事  你怎么会吃下一枚角币
What? How did you eat a dime?
豪斯
House.